I will read chat in 13 seconds.
30 seconds.
I'm reading chat.
I'm not looking at chat right now.
Okay, I'm looking.
Okay, now I'm looking at chat.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for my silliness.
I am indeed a goose, and I do indeed be silly.
What's going on, people?
I have decided, because I'm an adult and my mom isn't here, to drink beer.
Cheers.
And we will get only wins today.
No losses allowed.
Every time I lose, I will ban 10 people.
So you better hope I win.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
Ban me!
No, no, I'm not gonna ban anyone.
Come on.
Only if you misbehave, then I will ban you.
If you act in the wrong way, then you shall be banned.
I see someone right now misbehaving.
You know who you are.
Keep it up and you will receive a ban.
All of this is pre-recorded, yes.
Nothing is real, guys.
You should not believe anything on the internet.
The first lesson of the internet.
It's all scripted.
Is it me for writing in Arabic?
No, it's not you, Falfongo.
It was the person writing in that other language.
The script today is good.
It has been polished for many days.
This is why the stream was so delayed, guys.
I had to get the script perfect.
I don't wanna present you with a subpar script, you know?
It's a good one.
Fuck you, polished shit?
Man, that's a deep one.
People are not gonna get that one, you know that, right?
That's a deep cut.
I like it.
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
We have things to do today.
I unlocked a new character.
We need to look at that.
Here I am looking at you, boy.
Watch this.
Wait.
I think it was Eden.
Right?
Judas?
Yeah, this is the one.
I haven't played this one yet.
Okay, question mark hearts, question mark speed, question mark attack.
Ever changing.
So maybe every floor you get a randomized stat distribution.
That's fucked up, man.
That's my assumption at least.
Win streak is 2!
Nice!
Okay, we have unknown... Oh, we can't even see the hearts.
Oh, I'm gonna hate this character, guys.
Wait a minute, I'm gonna love this character, guys.
Oh, that's good.
Wait, is it randomized?
Every third?
No, yeah, it's randomized.
What is that little thing?
Stitches.
While held, grants a familiar that can be controlled with the attack buttons and deals minor contact damage to enemies.
Activation swaps places with the familiar.
This teleport grants a brief moment of invulnerability and can damage enemies and destroy some obstacles in direct contact with Isaac.
Interesting.
And the intruder inhabits Isaac's face and fires quad shots of slowing tears in addition to Isaac's normal tears.
But it doesn't say it's random, though.
Chance when taking damage to spawn blue spiders in this logic.
Yeah, but okay.
It's not every time I shoot.
Oh, there's an internal cooldown.
I see, I see.
And then I can move the little guy around with the... I see, I see how it is.
And then if I... Cool.
Wait, does that mean I can... Oh, I thought I could enter with this guy and then swap out on the other side.
It's too bad.
Oh, interesting.
That is weird, man.
Oh, that is actually kind of cool.
This feels more like a challenge and not actually a new character.
Right?
Like, this is weird.
This is actually super weird.
I guess it's about playing shotgun here.
Like that, you know?
I wonder if I can pick up items with this guy.
Oh, that's too bad.
But if I do this... Why can't I space bar?
Oh, okay.
I thought I could destroy obstacles or something.
Wait, what did it say about that?
Activation swaps it.
We damage enemies and destroy some obstacles and direct contact with Isaac.
So that means if I put this on an enemy and I click the button, it should be good.
Hey, look at this.
Oh!
I see the potential.
I didn't even think about that.
That's amazing.
I love it.
I see how it is.
Scapular.
This is the one when damage down to the last half part automatically gain a soul heart.
That's nice, actually.
Oh, we also have two tinted rocks so far.
It's a good way to stay alive.
Oh, god.
Wait, I can't teleport to him if he's out of sight.
Oh, never mind.
I can.
Very interesting concept for a character.
I like it, actually.
But it's not really destroying any obstacles.
Oh, wait, I gotta get this, too.
Where's my little guy?
Where did he go?
Oh, there.
There we go.
I got ten coins already.
Bible?
Ah, but do I want to switch out my whole deal here?
I don't know if I want to.
I'll save my money.
Save it.
Oh, god.
Wait, what the?
Oh, wait a sec now.
When you take damage, things happen.
Hold up, I need to kill these first and then think.
Tami's head fires a ring of ten.
Oh, no way!
Chance to... Okay, so every time we take damage, everything changes?
That's crazy.
Chance to fire concussive tears that confuse enemies.
Okay, and the headless baby.
Bro, I don't know.
This suddenly went kind of bad.
This may be a problem.
But, sure.
I wish I could see my HP, though.
That's a real bummer.
Step into my office.
Office!
You know, you like my office.
Good.
Stay in there.
Wonderful.
Oh, it's the worst item in the game!
I'm so unlucky.
But, you know, it doesn't matter because it's going to change.
Here's the thing.
Guys, this is the strategy with this character.
You don't care what items you pick up.
All you want to do is pick up as many items as you can.
That's what this character is about.
I like it.
So actually, this is pretty good.
What was the fork again?
He has to heal some health?
It's actually... No, I'll keep the coin, I guess.
I could grab a... Yeah, grab the Bible!
Because we want as many items as we... No, wait.
But that's an active.
No, never mind.
Never mind.
Unless the Bible is like a different category, meaning that if it gets switched, there's a higher chance it gets turned into something better.
You know what I mean?
Because the Bible is kind of... Nah, it's probably just an active.
It's like all of the actors.
Okay, let's go.
Cheers, guys.
Dude, look at Eden!
He was glitching the F out.
I don't know why I centered myself.
Oh my god, everything changed again!
We are now become... I don't know, Elvis?
I can see my heart's hallelujah.
Telepathy for dummies.
Depression 2020.
I mean, this is good.
I like it.
Wait, what did I have?
Homie tears.
Okay.
Let's just do it.
I believe.
Okay.
I'm happy with that.
We have a nice buffer here as well.
Guys, this character is actually a lot of fun.
I'm having a blast with this one.
2020 is crazy.
I can't take damage now because it's too good.
Oh yeah.
I'm rich.
Ah, that's an active, right?
We charge just one bar of X.
No, it's not.
Nice!
Good stuff.
I'm also going to take...
Wait, is my health being randomly changed as well when I take damage?
Because in that case...
Let's not take a pill.
I'm going to take this.
I believe.
I believe we're going to keep the hearts.
Oh, I wish I could teleport inside there now.
Crazy that I don't have any bombs.
Honestly, like what?
How?
That must be a record in how unlucky I am.
Unluckiest Isaac player of all time?
Wow.
Nearly lost all my items.
A pencil.
Oh, I like that one actually.
It doesn't matter.
We're just going to pick up whatever, right?
Because it becomes randomized item every time.
This is an insane character.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Totally chilling.
Wow, I'm so good.
I do wonder if the damage is going to also affect me when I'm... Oh, destroy this.
When I'm damaged by, you know, spikes and stuff like that.
Self-harm.
I guess I could find out, but let's not actually.
I like my current setup.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13.
Just have a little bit of a buffer.
We're going for the... now.
Ready?
Saw that.
Oh, they almost got hit there.
Let's activate this, by the way.
Wow!
Come on, homing tears.
Do your thing.
Oh!
This guy's unpredictable.
Crab cakes.
Whoa.
Nice.
That was so good.
Um, yeah.
Question is, are we going to go for Angel?
Dude, let's go for Angel.
Yeah, Angel is.
I like it.
But we're not done exploring, are we?
We are.
Wait, where's the shop?
Maybe I'll... no, no, no.
Just keep going.
This is good.
I like.
We're going, Angel.
Fight club.
It's risky, but there's a lot of chests here, so probably good.
Another buffer is good.
Activating my tears.
Oh God.
Nice.
Dude, I'm playing so well today.
Okay.
Scary.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, I died, I died, I died.
We got switched again.
What's happening?
Kidney Bean.
I like that one.
Hot bombs.
The wafer is good.
But now I can't see my HP.
Options.
Oh, that's good.
Actually, it doesn't matter for me.
PhD is good, I guess.
So while we have this, we go all pills.
Binky, yeah, whatever.
The question is, do we still have all our hearts?
I'm not sure we do.
The Bean is one of the best items.
Empress.
Oh!
Right, I gotta choose.
True.
Get away from me.
I should have bean them.
Okay, I want this.
Oh, that was great.
It was!
My friend!
Let's find a deco.
A deco tree.
That one.
Absolutely, yeah.
More items.
Okay.
I can choose to give up a bunch of blue hearts.
Ooh, money.
Oh, I have a magnet.
Nice.
It doesn't matter what I grab, I guess.
Chaos.
Ooh, that's actually nice.
I like that one a lot.
But it's going to be changed anyway, right?
So honestly, what I would want to do is to just grab as many cheap items as I can.
That's like the play.
Oh, let me see if I can heal.
Okay, I can't.
I'll take this.
Wait, why did that just happen?
Oh, it spawned some pickups.
Right, okay.
Pill.
Yeah, we want that since we have PhD now, right?
Yes.
Tears up.
Wonderful.
It spawned two red hearts.
Why not?
Got a battery in here as well.
I'm good.
Don't jump down.
Oh my god, I almost did.
Gotta be careful.
I want to find the rune that removes curse.
I couldn't do anything there.
That was nothing I could do.
Mom's purse.
Yo, one thing I wonder.
Let's say I get this one, right?
Which I do have now.
I have conjoined one of three.
But if I then switch all my items, is that going to count towards that?
Hmm.
Interesting.
A bar of soap, rubber cement, sticky bombs, stapler.
Okay, ladder's pretty cool.
Also, what do we have down there?
Grants and eternal heart at the start of each new floor!
Whoa!
Okay, we gotta stick with this configuration for a while, then.
Tis a good one.
I'm gonna go to the curse room.
Stop me.
Also, we just confirmed we did not change.
But it's only when you take enemy damage.
Right.
Wait, I can actually grab this.
If I need to.
Rubber cement.
The empress was damage.
Speed, okay.
Is there another way I can avoid using a bomb?
Whatever.
Okay, that was not worth it.
Trying to charge me?
Dude, I do a lot of damage.
If I could hit anyone.
It doesn't matter what I get.
Just pick everything up.
It really doesn't matter.
In fact, I think a lot of money on this character could be really good.
You want to buy as many items as possible, right?
Like here.
Why can't I see what that is?
Okay.
Bombs, coin purse, spawns for random pills.
Yes.
Oh wait, we don't have PhD anymore.
Crap.
I'm gonna eat him anyway.
Okay.
Good.
In case we didn't have full health, I don't know if we did.
Maybe we didn't.
I will actually go ahead and buy that HP.
Because I'm just very unsure when I can't see my HP.
I got a plate saved.
Come on, bro.
Uh-oh.
Boy.
Dude, I love the way my character looks right now.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
I'm gonna impress this bitch.
Let me impress upon you how much damage I will do.
There you go.
Wait, they're bouncing off sideways.
Also, it looks like I'm sort of auto aiming a little bit there.
I'm excited.
I actually don't mind that.
Whoa!
Okay, stay on the move.
Who's the master?
I'm the master.
Plus one health.
Here's what I think, guys.
I see the meta.
I see the way to do this.
You want to pick up as many plus health items as possible.
Because you get the immediate effect from that and the item will change later into something potentially better.
Think about it.
It's smart.
Okay, let's go.
It's the flooded caves.
Okay, so wait, why do we have an eternal heart right now?
Shouldn't that have been turned into a normal red heart?
Ah, no, wait, no, wait.
That's not how that works.
On the next floor it will, because we just got it from the trinket.
I see.
W ladder.
Oh god, oh god.
Almost took damage.
Ah, oh, oh, nice!
A louse, itchy, wait, what?
I can hold two trinkets.
Louse.
Small chance of spawning a blue spider any time Isaac is in a room with enemies.
I wonder how that works when I get rerolled.
Now that I have two trinkets.
Hmm, interesting.
Isn't it?
There we go.
I can't get over there, unfortunately.
Oh, not
bad.
I killed it.
Ah, man, I'm leaving behind.
I've left behind so many rooms.
It's going to be an annoying backtrack.
Easy.
Eight coins.
Let's wait.
Wow.
Wow!
Shit!
I got hit.
Dude, our HP is messed up!
It changes massively!
Whoa!
Shit, that didn't last very long!
I'm going to stop questioning what I have.
I'm just going to go.
Go, go, go.
And we got a little dude.
That's cool, I guess.
I'm just going to go with the flow, man.
We can't get committed to one build.
Okay, we're fine, we're fine.
That was actually pretty good.
Yes.
Do it!
My tongue is itchy!
Okay.
Again!
Dude, the little brim guy is actually kind of killing it.
He's making it happen.
Hey!
Sweetness.
Bar of soap?
Sure, why not?
Angel!
So here's my question.
If I pick this up now, I wonder if every time there's a reroll, my angel item becomes another angel item.
And not just a randomized item for multi-items that exist in the item world of items.
Okay.
Oh, wait, it's one of these.
Yes, do it now.
Nice.
There must be some kind of thing that carries over, you know, between these rerolls in terms of health.
Oh, no!
Why does that happen?
We are now different!
We do something different.
No idea what's happening right now.
It doesn't feel good.
Shit!
Oh, no, we changed again.
You bastard!
Okay.
Nice!
That got a little bit hairy.
PPs.
What is this thing I have right now?
Butterbean.
I don't like that very much.
I like this one more.
I like pills.
This run is just a mess.
Oh, we can see Secret Rooms now.
That's cool.
Must have gotten some kind of item that does that.
Let me quickly review.
Right, rage.
Black handle.
Sack of pennies.
Okay.
What?
Chaos.
Alright.
Right.
Let's go back and backtrack a little bit.
Do I... Yeah, let's go in here.
We got some kind of mushroom.
Grant's an extra life, but that's not gonna actually work.
Because it's gonna reroll.
Unless the extra lives stay.
I guess we'll find out.
I need a bit more money.
Oh, I got hit!
Wait.
What the hell is this?
Oh, delirium.
Okay.
Bloody lust.
I think I have an idea of what's happening.
I don't.
But I think I do.
But I don't.
I go with the flow.
We got money!
I'm going back.
I want one extra life.
Oh, secret here.
Want keys?
You can have one key.
Two keys.
Okay, three keys.
Nice!
More.
That's my last.
I gotta keep at least one key on me.
Wait, I'm tempted.
Do it.
Shit!
I hate it!
Ew!
Oh man, I'm gonna be so lost.
Why did I do this?
I hate these inanimate objects!
Okay.
Less tears, no thanks.
I wonder if pill effects are randomized as well every time I take damage.
Huh?
I have no HP.
It's over.
Keep her.
Use that.
Oh my god, man.
Oh!
At least I can fly now.
I think there's definitely some carryover in terms of HP.
Meaning that if you lose a bunch of HP, you're gonna get less every time you re-roll.
It's probably just the type of heart that gets re-rolled, you know?
So if you have 10 hearts, all 10 get re-rolled into random hearts.
That's what I think.
Then again, we had two hearts before and now we have one, and we didn't take...
Like, I'm not so sure.
We're done here.
I hate to say it, but we gotta go!
Oh, we got AWAS!
Fuck.
I saw too late.
Okay, at least we got an extra heart there.
That's good.
AWAS... I don't... I have shit, you know?
That's definitely a floor deco.
Yeah!
Oh no, it's the sprinkler!
Hmm...
It's an active, it's gonna replace my current one, it's not gonna add to the pool I have.
Terrible.
I need money.
What?
Oh, oh yeah, I can fly!
Uh... use bird foot?
No.
I want this.
Oh, hell no.
Am I fast?
I'm pretty fast.
Yeah!
Oh sh... Oh, we're doing this now.
Dude, I like it.
This is like that challenge.
I'm an expert at this.
I will never again take damage.
Wait, what?
Shouldn't that be like a...
Ah, there, okay.
Uh oh.
Nice.
Wait, I'm eating rocks?
Sweet!
What else has changed?
Let me see what else I got.
We gotta stay on this guy!
This is insane.
Uh... okay, key piece looks like it just stays.
Battery, store sub... nice!
Thunder thighs, yeah, break most things.
Whoa, oh, right, okay.
Spewer, blue man, robo baby.
Okay, okay, okay, cool.
Um...
Let's go do that other secret room.
Dude, this is great.
I'm loving this.
Whoo!
No, we changed!
No!
Fuck!
Wait, what do we have now?
I can't read all this every time, man.
Too much work.
Um...
I'll take this.
I like that.
I'm trying to look at the icons on the right, see if I can actually see what's going on right now.
I had a feeling that would happen.
Okay.
Oh wait, we got the shitty item!
Shard of glass!
Is terrible.
Oh wait, I was gonna go to the secret room.
That was the whole point.
I got ten bombs, that's nice.
That's not gonna do anything for me.
Like, it doesn't even matter how much HP you have.
Dude, are you fucking serious?
Wait, what's happening now?
Guess I'll do that.
How come this thing always comes back?
Belly button.
Wait, two trinkets at a time!
Okay, okay.
Under thighs.
Oh man, this... my brain can't handle this, guys.
This is... whoa.
Whoo!
Oh, we got some kind of toxic now, that's why they lost HP.
Dude, my attack rate is in the dumpster.
This is horrible.
This is the worst.
Kinda wanna take damage on purpose.
But there's no reason to do that.
I'm just gonna wait for it to happen naturally.
Wow, painful.
Boiled baby, that's cool.
More the better.
More, more, more, more, more.
That's what it's all about.
Ha!
He got shot by the inanimate object.
That'll teach him.
Pro gamer.
Whoa!
Yeah!
Thanks.
It's Loki!
I'm gonna mess him up with my slow ass projectiles.
Bet it'll be good.
Dude, I kinda wanna get hit here.
It's pain.
There we go!
I gotta see this.
C-section.
Replaces tears with a charge attack that fires floating fetuses.
These feeder shots last a few seconds and the whole man on enemies.
Whoa!
Okay.
Hit a play.
Alright, alright.
Breath of life.
Right.
Cool.
Wait, what is it with my attack?
Why is my attack so weird?
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Wait, what?
I don't understand this attack.
Hold on, what?
Replaces tears with a charge attack that fires...
These fetuses shot last a few seconds and the whole man on enemies.
Okay.
Gimme.
Gimme this one.
And...
Go back.
Unfortunately, we're not done here.
We gotta find as many items as we can.
It's the name of the game.
I don't know if I like this attack.
Hold on, I got hit!
Oh no, we got some kind of shitty effect.
Some kind of planetary stuff is going on right now.
Uh, north.
Honestly, it's fine.
Oh my god!
What is happening?
Who's onto me?
It's you!
What the fuck is happening?
Stop questioning it, just go.
Oh yeah, eat him.
Eat him, eat him.
I don't know what I'm shooting, some kind of brown poop that swirls.
Swirly brown poop.
I'm doing okay damage actually.
Not bad.
I don't know what's going on, but it's okay.
Oh, that's money.
Hey!
Okay, wait, wait, I like this.
Me like.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna go down here actually.
Ah, wait, we don't have any HP!
Wait, we do.
Wonderful.
Money.
Ah!
Wait, what the hell is that?
Jar of wisps.
Spawns orbital wisp familiars equal to the number on this item's icon?
Stars at two wisps and increase.
Okay.
I don't like that.
I don't like it.
I thought I said crack Jesus for a second.
Okay, let's just move on.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm also camouflaged I guess.
No, wait, wrong way.
This is a mess.
This run is an absolute mess.
I'm scared of what will happen next.
I don't even have a plan, honestly, of where to go or what to do on this run.
I'm just gonna go.
Maybe kill Isaac or something.
Let's get in here.
Actually huge.
Curse of the log, you know, thanks.
Soulheart, that's huge.
Wait, I got homing tears.
Oh, that's nice.
We have some sort of.
Poison thingy.
I kind of like the setup right now.
It's weird, but it's it's cool.
I want to keep it.
Nevermind.
I don't get to keep it.
Guys, use this before I die.
I mean, before I switch again.
We got some kind of wisp now.
Extension cord has appeared.
Whatever you say.
I like doing that.
Friend zone.
I mean, I do pretty good damage, honestly.
I may not even need to.
I almost got hit.
We got some kind of magic fingers.
Assumes a coin.
Damn, no.
Bad guess.
Nope.
Guys, I'm going to donate.
We're going to work on donations today.
I have decided it.
Was that in the game?
I'm actually not sure that was in the game.
I don't know if you even heard that.
I don't know if you probably think I'm.
No, wait, something's happening.
It's like a wolf howling or something.
What the fuck is happening?
Oh, we got the delirium.
Yo.
Let's get to the boss fast.
I want to use it there.
I hate whatever setup I have going right now.
It's terrible.
It is atrociously bad.
Okay, there we go.
What the hell is this?
Bro, are you...
Drop this trinket.
No, actually keep it because if we get hit again, you know, we want to keep it.
I have almost no damage with this one.
Wow.
Little larva.
Magician.
Oh, I like that.
Wait, chaos card?
What the heck is that?
Oh, throws a card in the direction.
Isaac is moving, killing.
Really?
Hold on.
Oh, we also have the moon.
Yo, I'm shooting mega fast right now and I have a lot of damage.
That's a lot of bombs.
99 luv balons.
Go back.
We also have the wisps.
Wait, what?
Oh.
Wait, what's happening?
What am I doing?
Response oral...
Why am I taking damage?
Bro, I have no idea what's happening.
Oh no, oh no, I'm dead.
I can't, this room.
I can't.
Go.
Oh, man.
Kill him.
Yikes.
Okay, healing, good, good.
I'm gonna chaos card this guy.
Or, gal.
It actually works on bosses.
That's crazy.
Wait, can I pick it up again?
Oh, too bad.
I am going to...
take this.
I'm gonna go up.
Trinity shields.
Oh, I already had one, I guess.
Nice.
But it doesn't matter.
Blow him up.
Don't get hit, don't get hit.
I don't know what's happening.
We're going.
Wish me luck.
Oh, man.
You turn off.
Holy map.
Guys, I will do this entire map without taking a single point of damage.
But in order to do that, I need to study my situation.
Rocket in a jar.
Okay, okay.
Scanning, scanning, scanning.
Scanning.
We're not gonna take damage.
It's okay.
Interesting.
Spider butt!
Look
at you bouncing over there.
Oi!
There we
go.
That was kind of a wild room.
I'm gonna do the left side first.
What did I take damage from?
I'm bleeding.
Oh, no.
Find hearts.
Crystal ball.
Spawn a card.
Tower.
Let's do it.
I'm taking damage.
What's happening?
Okay, okay.
We're doing this now.
I'm still bleeding.
Heal me, heal me, heal me.
I see, I see a heart.
It's not here.
What the fuck is happening?
It's over.
I'm dead.
I can't heal.
Take damage.
I need to take damage.
We gotta take damage.
Hit me.
I died.
I thought I would get randomized HP from that.
Bro, what?
Wait, okay.
I'm gonna go again here.
Coupon.
I like that.
I mean, none of these are gonna matter.
I wonder.
Speed.
If I...
Wait.
I can get infinite items here.
Maybe.
Let's pay attention.
So we have 0.85 speed.
Let's see if that changes when we take damage.
Fucking shard of glass can suck it!
Ruined everything.
It's like the worst item ever.
Unbelievable trash tier.
It's not a good thing.
It's like a debuff to get that item.
It's free!
Donate a single coin.
There you go.
That's on me.
Wait, I'm also doing random damage.
Why is my nails rusty?
Oh, it's the randomized effect.
I hate that.
Okay, I still...
My speed changed!
So pills are randomized!
All dead.
Go again.
I don't know if I like this character, guys.
This is pure fucking chaos.
And with the D4 as well, what are we doing here?
You know?
Come on.
Okay.
I don't even know what that item is.
Is it spawning bombs?
Yeah.
Here.
Give me the ass scooper.
The flush nerd.
Let's go left.
No!
I still have a big guy left.
Aewas?
No, Ansys.
That's actually pretty good.
We don't have a bomb.
Oh no, wait, this is the guy that drops the shitty item, right?
Alright, it doesn't matter.
Not on this character.
What?
What do I have now?
Okay.
No.
Good.
What?!
Okay, I don't want to play this character.
It's not fun, man.
I don't want to not be able to have any semblance of a build going.
Let's go with something else.
New character.
Let's go with...
Let me see here.
Maybe Isaac, actually.
Or Apollyon.
We could try Apollyon.
Or actually, normal Eden is kind of fun too.
Let's do this one.
Let's do that one.
It's been a while since I played this one.
I feel like I've gotten a lot better since I played him.
Let's see if we can make anything happen.
I mean, the damage is solid here.
It's not bad.
This one's kind of diabolical.
Nah, we're good.
So, the main objective right now is to find HP up.
Man, no money at all yet.
Just run into me.
Beautiful.
Okay, one coin.
Let's do the boss.
This guy again?
He's weird, man.
Dude, please stay still.
This has to be the most annoying boss.
There we go.
Ah, it's over, it's over, it's already over.
Lost two hearts already, this is...
Fucking t- Pfft, start over, man.
What an absolute dumpster start.
Oh, I have no keys.
This thing is not that good.
But it's not the worst.
The thing is though, it activates when you take damage.
And on this character, you really don't want to take damage.
I'm gonna get a lot of flies from these poops.
I'm gonna stay at range so I don't waste my flies.
That's the strategy.
I need the item that gives me coins when I destroy poops.
Now that would be a crazy combo.
No, my flies are being wasted.
Dammit.
Can't really do anything about it.
Destroy that.
Definitely taking that.
That's actually huge.
HP, HP, HP.
Name of the game.
Come on, then.
Great start.
Very nice.
Garglings, oh man, these guys are tough.
I'm gonna lose HP here.
This is probably one of the hardest bosses you can have in the start.
I don't know how to do this without taking damage.
It is fucking crazy how difficult this one is.
Hey, my bird is doing work.
Nice.
I'm glad I picked out that blue heart, otherwise I would have been a two right now.
And I would have hated life.
But this is good.
Move on.
The plan is to get home.
With a key.
And open a door.
So we need to find a teleporter.
More money.
Also, what's happening with my body?
Oh, it's this experimental treatment.
Okay.
That was actually a bad experimental treatment.
I lost damage on it.
Crap, oh my god.
Jesus!
Wow.
No, don't go to shop.
Not yet.
It's not time yet.
This way.
Come on.
The flies are helping me quite a bit here.
Nah, this is...
Wow.
Dude, why
is the game so difficult today?
Like, what's up with these fucking rooms?
I feel like it's way harder than usual.
Wow.
I was fighting for my life just now.
Come here.
Don't jump at me at life speed.
Okay.
Dude, we haven't even found the treasure room.
We gotta go back.
It's of course in the one spot I didn't look.
I'm actually going here just to see.
Sometimes there's fires you can destroy for money.
Oh.
Speed down, range is building?
Wait, what?
Okay.
I don't like that one, actually.
This is an L.
Yeah.
There's no way I'm taking those coins.
Too risky.
Pause time and then move on.
I don't remember what he does.
Oh, right, that one.
It's not too bad.
This one is manageable.
Wait, what?
Nice.
Dinner is huge!
Oh, by the way, we can't get red hearts.
That was the whole gimmick with this one.
For some reason I remembered you started with three blue and you could take it from there, but that's not how it works.
Obviously we do angels on this one.
There's just no other thing you can do.
I mean, you can, but I'm not gonna.
So honestly, HP up items are kind of bad for me.
I'd rather have like a damage buff.
Yeah.
I like that.
And that was so huge as well that we just got that.
Why is that happening, by the way?
Oh, it's Taurus, of course.
I'm gonna try and keep moving here so I can get the Taurus.
Wait, is it only when I move or...
No, it's just when I'm in the room, okay.
There we go.
Okay, maybe I do like this, guys.
This is pretty good.
Another blue heart, dude.
This is a great start now.
That's what I was waiting for.
Boom.
You can probably use that as well to get through doors where you take damage.
If you time it right.
It lasts a long time, too.
Oh, I hate this guy.
They're so unpredictable.
Okay, the Taurus has kind of been saving my ass.
Not bad.
Wait, check this out.
Oh, what?
Why doesn't that work?
It worked before.
Shit.
Okay, whatever.
Angel time, come on.
33% chance.
Can it happen?
Will it happen?
Nice.
It only happens once, I think.
Actually, maybe it does build up again.
Ah, that was bad.
At least my bird is here now.
Okay.
Ah, man, not this again.
No angel.
No treasure room, either.
What?
I'm gonna go up.
There it is.
I need Taurus to activate now.
Beautiful.
I'm kind of dependent on that.
Ah, this one.
I feel like that's so unlucky.
Where are my stat items?
Oh, man, I can't even get in there.
Wow, that took a while.
No.
Oh, wait, can I?
No, I can't even destroy that.
Took forever.
Motherfucker!
I want to make a bridge!
There we go.
And then I have to look at my fucking balls dangling from my neck as well while I walk.
This is purgatory.
Look at this red nutsack.
Just flopping.
You're mine.
Good.
Stepping would be crazy on this character.
I guess it would also be crazy to go into the curse room on this character.
I am crazy.
But I have a plan, you'll see what I mean.
I'm gonna wait a bit.
Hey!
Not bad.
Even got lock-up as well.
Let's leave.
Oh, I forgot that I can have black hearts on this character too.
For some reason I thought they would all be blue.
There you go.
So far so good.
Although I will need to find some damage.
Cause it's just been HP, HP, HP until now.
And that just won't do.
Like look at this, I do no damage.
If it wasn't for my Taurus, I think I would be screwed.
Damn.
Oh, thank you bird.
Ah!
Let me in!
I don't know why that doesn't work.
Like any obstacle should make a bridge, right?
Mushrooms, rocks...
Poop, wait.
Yeah, this way first.
The whiz...
Ah!
Poop!
You can't win the game like this, guys.
This is almost restart time.
There's just no point.
You don't get any damage items, you can't do anything.
I need Epikak.
Or something else that gives me a massive damage bonus.
Wait a sec.
Oh, wait, we got a Poop, we got a fly generator in here.
Wait, don't, nevermind.
It doesn't work like that.
You can't create infinite flies like that.
These flies are so short-lived.
Okay, come on.
Six, seven percent chance of Angel.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh!
Okay, come on.
More tears.
Random heart.
Ooh, that's so lucky.
But we need damage, come on.
We need damage now.
It's more survivability.
Mmm.
Can't even bomb these guys, that's unfortunate.
What if I poop on them?
Do they get angry?
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna go back.
Mamma Mia!
Okay, at least we got some bombs, that's actually really needed.
Where's the store?
I have money.
I can't wait to wing wing on these guys.
I'm just gonna wait for that, actually.
Wing wing!
Love it!
He's gonna smoke skeleton?
Oh, okay.
Poop.
Ah!
There we go!
I know there was a skeleton somewhere.
Crap.
The good news about the mantle is that you can always just enter these.
There's no fear.
That's really nice.
Wait, I need to blow these up.
Poop.
Okay, come on, something good.
Oh, you can re-roll time!
You ready?
Ooh, wait, wait, wait.
Friends are falling familiar with a randomized appearance.
That's more damage.
This one could potentially be more damage on pills in the future.
This is a long-term plan.
We can potentially get both if we find enough money.
I think for now I'm gonna take the PhD.
Oh wait, apparently a pill spawns, right?
Explosive diarrhea drops one lit bomb per second for...
Wait, that's considered a good pill?
I don't know if it is, man.
That seems like a bad thing.
Who wants diarrhea?
Not me, but then again, who wants cancer?
A lot of people, apparently.
In this game.
I need money.
I need two more coins.
Surely we can find that.
I'm just gonna explosive diarrhea here.
Actually, that is pretty good.
I do like...
I don't think we're gonna find the coins!
Oh, no.
I could step on that.
That is risky business.
I'm gonna do it.
There we go.
That was a very expensive item.
But it may be worth it.
Remember, parts are temporary, items are forever.
Yoink!
Wait, wait, why does he have a helmet on?
Oh, it's just a random one.
Okay.
That looks funny.
I really wish I could take that.
Okay, wait, wait, secrets!
Here!
Has to be.
Let me check the other sides first.
Let me be absolutely sure.
Okay, it's looking good.
And from here...
That's good!
I think we are good!
Fuck yeah!
Ah, I don't like this.
Okay, fine.
Ah, well.
Terrible.
Why did I gamble?
Why did I do that?
It's a bad idea.
Alright, let's get the hell out of here.
Okay.
Man, I need some damage.
Like, that familiar's not gonna do it for me.
It ain't enough.
Oh, crap.
Very unfortunate room.
Sir.
Battery... yeah.
It's not gonna do anything for me, is it?
Is it?
Shouldn't that immediately make a poop available, though?
Infinite poopage?
Maybe it would be a little too broken, but, you know...
It says it restores the final charge!
I don't know.
I feel like I'm being lied to here.
Now we go right.
Oh, my God.
This one's gonna be hell on Earth.
Yeah.
Guys, I may actually die in this room.
This is the end of the run.
This room is just too fucking crazy.
Yeah, yeah!
Come on!
Oh!
I forgot I had Taurus.
That saved my ass.
Insane room.
Dude, they won't die.
I'm cooked.
What the fuck is that?
You heard that?
The west.
This map is confusing me right now.
I don't understand what's happening.
I feel like I'm going insane.
Take him out.
Suck on that one.
We're gonna get another speed boost in a second.
I think?
Maybe not, actually.
Maybe that overrode.
Bro, what the hell?
Where's my Taurus?
This room is gonna kill me, guys.
Yeah, yeah, Taurus!
Finally, it works.
Really could have needed you in that other room.
Oh no, is that the troll bomb one?
You know what?
It's so bad, I'll keep the book.
I mean, the poop.
I'm gonna donate all my money, if this run's about to end.
If I don't find any damage before Mom, I don't know what to do.
It doesn't matter what crazy items I find.
If there's no damage, there's no win.
I'm gonna wait for the... there we go.
Health up.
Yeah, honestly, go!
Just do it!
Oh no.
Nice.
Load up, nice!
Ah, chances...
Again, we get it.
I may as well just quit this run right now, dude.
It's useless.
Move on.
Okay.
Why are we only at 16% uh... angel here?
Shouldn't that be way higher?
Get them all, get them all quick.
Oh!
Taurus has been carrying this entire run.
And to think I wasn't even happy about Taurus at first.
Another bomb.
Oh no.
Wait, is he like bugging out if I'm too far away?
Okay, that's huge.
That damage is what we need for Mom.
The problem is, I need to go in with a teleport for Mom!
We can't have this!
Damn!
My one shot at damage.
I can't even take it.
Feels bad, man.
Oh!
That's right.
Oh my god, man.
Really?
Yeah, you know what, I'll take this instead.
Plate safe.
Ah, crap!
I don't have a key!
I'll be back.
Nice!
Oh, that was actually kind of cool.
Key me.
Right now.
This is rough.
That was crazy.
Pills.
Range?
Range.
Oh, nice!
Good pills, good pills.
That's something.
That's indirect damage we get there.
Keep pooping.
That actually blew up the door frame.
Come on, charge me!
Well, that's a dead end.
Still no teleport.
We got a key, though.
Actually, we can enter both the treasure room and the chest room now.
That's huge.
There better be some good damage now.
I need it.
Or a teleport card.
I'll take both.
Okay.
That's something.
Wait.
Actually, I don't mind the tick.
The tick is good.
I'll take that.
What is this?
No.
Useless!
Haven't gone to the shop yet, either.
But I don't have a key now.
And I think I needed a key to get in there.
With six coins.
Can't really do much.
Well.
That's the end of that, I guess.
Crap!
Not much you can do.
The Empress.
I've misclicked!
Well, it's not going to help much, anyway.
No, I lost the mantle.
Oh, God.
She pushed the bomb into me.
Honestly, dude, that run was excruciatingly annoying to play.
Didn't find any damage from start to finish.
Terrible.
Not much you can do, man.
Okay.
Let's hope for no HP up.
Gotta rely on that RNG.
This one's good, though.
If I can get my HP up via that one, and then get my damage from the boss item, maybe.
Would be nice to buy that heart, actually.
Okay, bomb there is huge.
The mulligan!
Spawn of bluefly.
Hey!
That doesn't sound too bad.
It's something.
That is pretty much just a damage boost, actually.
When you hit an enemy, chance of spawning one and the fly is going to immediately attack the enemy, right?
So it's kind of a chance for extra damage on attack.
We can think of it that way.
Well...
Wait, wait, wait.
No, I'm going to go back and grab this now.
Yeah.
Eternal heart now.
And now we pray for a decent item from the boss.
And we're going angel again, of course.
That's not a bad boss.
Never mind, he's modified.
Alright, it's not too bad.
Sick.
Yeah, there we go!
That's what I'm talking about, baby.
Nice.
Good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
It's a good start.
Then we get the extra HP up from the elemental heart.
Let's destroy this poop.
Get him out of here.
Sick.
And a bomb, that's so huge.
Always have at least one bomb.
Uh oh.
That was scary.
Vogue up.
Fantastic.
Come to me, I don't come to you, you come to me.
This is the rule.
Actually, I'm going to blow this up.
Nice.
Bro, I don't know how to traverse this room without taking damage.
Good thing we have the Book of Revelations for that.
To offset that.
Any tiny bit of shot speed actually feels so good to have.
It matters so much.
Okay, one bomb, we could maybe look for a secret.
But let's wait a bit.
Uh, there you are.
It's scary when you can't see where the enemies are.
Nice, keep healing up.
This book is going to be the one that saves the run.
Oh, it feels so good.
There it is.
Uh, Cube of Meat.
Yeah, not great.
Let's...
We actually have a... Dude, with Book of Revelations...
I think we could maybe go for demons, guys.
Because we can keep supplying.
I think I'm going to do it.
False PhD.
Uh, buh buh buh buh buh buh buh.
It's only one blue heart, man.
Like, this is totally worth.
Feels one heart of damage to Isaac turns into a full health pill.
That's...
wait.
Is this not just really good for me?
It just turned a blue heart into a black heart?
Oh, no, wait.
I guess it's a black heart into a black heart.
Okay.
Uh, chance to be revived with half of... That's also good.
I take it.
I take that.
We're going demons because of the Book of Revelations.
This is the strategy.
Let me check out some more things here.
I got five keys.
We can have a look around.
We have 800 coins in the machine.
Something probably happens at a thousand.
Let me quickly check for a secret room.
Okay, that looks good.
Not that one, though.
Oh, fuck that.
No, no, no.
Nope.
I'm leaving.
Get out of here.
Floor three, and it's going really well.
This is a fantastic start on the blue boy.
Oh, there's a guy behind me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
Fine.
Oh, we have XL going on right now.
XXL, XXL.
I think you motherfuckers need some help.
Damn it.
Nice.
Okay, we're going to get another blue heart here in a second.
Batteries are amazing in this run, by the way.
But we need... we want batteries.
Or anything that amplifies my regeneration of charges would also be beautiful.
Dude.
Get this guy out of here.
I want flying.
I mean, who doesn't?
Can't go in there.
For... yeah, that's worth.
Especially when you have extra keys.
I don't know how to dodge that.
I really don't.
Thank God for the book.
Smelly penny?
Rock penny?
What is it?
The cherry is nice.
Burnt penny.
Why is it smelly then?
25% chance to spawn a bomb when I pick up a coin?
Oh, but it's a... it's not a troll bomb.
It's a good... it's a good bomb.
I like that.
No, not this.
Ah, okay.
It's not that bad.
Yes.
It is potentially damage, right?
Tiny batteries.
A lot of them.
Four coins.
Yeah.
I'm too... oh, oh my... my beloved, my beloved, my beloved.
I need it.
Let's save up for it.
Dude, I can get it.
I'm gonna get it.
I'm doing it.
Can't stop me.
Boom!
I can't... I can't lose now.
I can't.
This is gonna be so good.
We're gonna get back to 800 soon again.
You might not... okay, come on.
Stay in the center.
What an annoying asshole.
That was tough.
I could grab this battery over here.
But I'm not gonna.
Actually, am I?
No, there's still stuff to clear.
I was like, if I can't find any more charges, then maybe I'll do it.
God, having the HP bars is so good!
I can actually plan things.
Like, I knew I had... I could back up there, you know?
Because I knew who would die.
Such a good item.
Spider mod.
Ooh, what's that?
Wait, anti-gravity!
See what we'll hover in place while...
Leasing attack button.
Ah, I don't know, man.
This is actually bad for me.
Actually, is it?
It's like saving up tears and then releasing them all at once.
I think it's bad.
Maybe I'll come back.
We'll see.
It does give me one tears, which is kinda crazy.
You can stack them up fast.
Ah, I got frozen.
But yeah, I'm gonna probably hate that.
Not being able to run and gun, you know?
Like this.
Would be devastating.
Now, if it was that thing where you charge up the attack and then release a bunch of shots at the same time, that I would go for.
Because then I'm not relying on staying in one place, you know?
Charging it up.
I can take them with me.
Oh, that was a friend.
My absolute favorite thing about spider mod is that it declutters the screen.
Even though there's more stuff on screen, it's easier to see who's an enemy and who's not, you know?
It's so nice.
Uh, yeah.
38% chance of a demon.
You know what?
Let's keep exploring because we can actually increase that percentage a little bit by bombing certain people.
And I will be bombing them.
We're gonna extract every bit of juice as we can.
I was hoping for a mushroom.
Or, I mean, a pill.
Yeah, some of these tiers I'm shooting do way more damage because of the randomized effect on them sometimes.
Like, my standard is 3.45 right now, but sometimes I do 7.
Okay.
This is the one with XL, so there's gonna be two bosses.
I'm actually tempted to go to the curse room.
We also have a bad... Actually, yeah, you know what?
Let's do that.
We have a battery where we can get another blue heart.
The book of Revelations will carry us here.
It'll be okay.
You can try this at home.
You can be just like me.
This way.
Actually, uh, do this first.
If there's fighting in here, we're gonna get one last...
Charge.
Nice.
Oh, that's a good item too!
That's damage, I think.
Huge!
I'm glad I went in here.
Okay, since I have a black heart, we're gonna chariot this one.
Wonderful.
Just to conserve the black heart, you know?
This is such a good one!
5.45 damage is amazing.
And then we leave, or at least we do the bosses.
It looks like I have a bib on, you know?
A little heart bib.
Pestilence.
I just did a quest the other day in Red Dead called Pestilence.
Oh!
Oh, I almost got hit by that.
Wait, uh, ice, ice, baby.
Sick.
Wait, I can!
Okay, maybe if we get it fully charged, it'll be good, but damn, I don't want this.
I don't want this cube of meat.
I really don't.
Gertie!
What's up, Gertie?
Almost got hit there.
Amazing.
Mom's pearls.
Yeah, that's okay.
It's actually decent.
Oh, ho, ho, ho!
The pact, I like!
Ghost baby, I like!
I do!
It's not bad.
It's good.
Book of Revelations, Book of Revelations.
Uh, we also gotta find a teleport, by the way.
This needs to happen soon.
Very soon.
Necropolis.
We're gonna explode the ice.
There we go.
Oh, wait, how are we gonna...
Oy!
Fragmented card?
Uh, do I like that more?
I think I do.
What's up, Mom?
Wow, wow!
Calm down!
Wait, marked!
Ooh, I don't know if I like this, guys!
This one is a... is a... is a... trade-off.
Maybe if I have... maybe if I have my mouse.
But I don't.
But actually, mouse is worse.
Guys, I'm gonna go for it.
I think it's okay.
We gotta learn this.
At some point, we gotta learn this.
Okay, so do I go in there?
Yes, I do.
Let's go south.
Wait, is he reacting to my movement?
Oh, crap!
Huh?
What just exploded?
I'm not sure what happened there.
There's some kind of battery device?
That could maybe be good.
Healing damage to enemies gradually recharges.
Ooh, we may have to get that one, guys.
But we need money first.
We don't have it.
I couldn't even hit anything there.
Keep exploring.
Treasure room has... no, we have found treasure room.
Damn, I was hoping for more.
Oh my goodness!
Holy shit!
Whew!
Less speed, more damage.
I think I like that.
I do, I do, I like it.
That's a decent trade-off.
I'm gonna sacrifice a bomb.
Big.
Wonderful.
I'm starting to maybe regret picking up the mark.
We'll see how it goes.
Oh god!
Okay, we're fine, we're fine.
Christ!
Like fish in a barrel.
Nah.
By the way, where's all the tinted rocks at?
That's what I wanna know.
Not bad.
I could blow that up.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm just happy I have damage, that's all.
But we gotta find teleport, this is the problem right now.
If we don't find teleport, we can't go home.
So... rip, actually.
Fuck me, we can't do anything.
Unless I miss something in the shop, let's go back and look.
Maybe there's something I didn't see there.
And of course, secret rooms.
Nah, oh no.
Wait, tears fire dang, no.
I mean, I could get, oh wait, I could almost get this.
Yes!
I'll take that.
Let's go look for secrets.
This is not it.
Not it here.
I think maybe, wait, what was that?
No.
Maybe down here.
No, wow.
Maybe in here.
Yeah, maybe.
Shit.
Other side, maybe.
No.
Dude, what?
Ah, wait, maybe in the south.
That looks good.
Ah, what?
Right side, maybe?
Right side?
Down?
Okay.
And then here?
Could be.
Very nice.
Unfortunately, no cards.
Damn.
Do we have any way to...
do anything here?
Let me think about this.
Spider much.
Shit.
Guys, I think we're cooked here.
We can't even go home.
Wait, what is that room with the...
with the little light in it?
Oh, okay.
No.
All right, go to boss.
Oh, wait, what?
It's not Mom!
Fuck!
Actually, I mean, good.
It's good.
It's good that it's not Mom.
Bro, will you please stand up?
Will the real one, please?
Stand up.
Come on, man.
There we go.
Tube of meat again.
And demon.
Too spooky is good!
Oh, wait, wait.
This one could be very interesting.
I think at the start of each floor, they're pleading as many red hearts as it can.
Staff grants bonus damage and speed for the rest of the floor.
Oh, but wait, I don't have any red hearts, so it's actually bad.
That one.
Okay, I'm happy with that.
Go!
Okay, we have the damage now.
Now is Mom.
This is the Mom one.
Please, we need a cart.
Cart me.
Oh!
I should have taken that, actually.
I should have waited until I had a fully empty bar.
Oh!
I regret taking the mark.
It makes it harder.
Tears are wider.
Yeah, I like it.
Don't make it easier to hit.
Fight club is closed.
Actually, it's the big boys' fight club.
DBFC.
That one is not dependent on hearts.
I don't know what it depends on.
Something.
Alright, let's go south first.
Oh, shit!
I'm getting a lot of battery out of this.
The volt battery is good.
Oh, wait, I didn't mean to...
Okay.
I accidentally picked it up, but why doesn't it say what it does?
I think it said tears up.
But other than that, I'm not really sure.
Wait, what?
Oh, we have confusion.
Health down.
Wait, let me think.
Guys, this is actually good.
Health.
That's a solid trait.
I can't believe it.
That's so good.
Oh, cart!
Ooh, we need money.
Money, money, money.
Oh, shit.
Less shot speed, tears collide with and destroy enemies.
I like that.
We need a lot of money now, so we can keep re-rolling, re-rolling, re-rolling cards.
My tears look insane.
Nice!
Health down me!
Don't enter the boss room.
Not yet.
Yeah.
Yeah, we can trade a key for a bomb.
By the way, I just realized a new technique.
Check this out.
I'm all the way over here.
If I want to shoot left fast, I do that.
See that?
Wait, what?
Oh, confusion.
Right.
We've been there before.
The tower?
Ooh, not quite what we need.
I'm actually gonna go in here.
Unlucky.
Oh, man.
Eight coins?
I would love a bit more.
Ah, we still have stuff up here.
This way.
Um, wait a minute.
Oh, confusion.
Right.
There's nothing I want here.
This is bad.
Um, is this open now?
It's open.
Oh, wait, that's not it.
I was...
yeah.
Never mind.
Guys, we have to gamble like crazy now.
The ultimate gamble.
I need all the luck I can get.
Wait, how the...
Oh.
This way.
I was legitimately so confused just now.
This way then.
Then here.
Damn.
Well, that's it.
That was that.
Pack it up, boys!
Wait, what?
What is... is that a bomb?
What is that?
Oh, it is a bomb.
Okay.
Rip.
Maybe I can destroy some rocks.
Hopefully something spawns.
We gotta look for tinted rocks or something.
Or even more secrets.
Yeah, secrets is what we need.
I wish I could know how to get into the fight room.
Or maybe some skulls, actually.
They sometimes spawn things.
Let's get these three.
Oh!
Too bad.
Damn.
That's horrible.
Let's look for a bigger collection of skulls.
Why are they so spread apart?
Oh, here we go.
Motherfucker!
That's how you do it.
Okay, now we go south and east.
Wait, no, I keep getting confused by this frickin' path.
This way.
And here we are.
Let's do this.
Mom!
That was good damage.
Whoa.
Good damage.
Well, it doesn't matter what I take here, I'm gonna take this.
No angels, though, unfortunately.
Unfortunately.
Uh...
Oh, we actually teleported to a different secret room.
Check that out.
Interesting.
Uh, wait, where do I...
Wait, hold on.
I have to go through here.
Oh, what the hell, man.
That's evil.
I think it's over here.
No, wait, where's the entrance?
More to the west, I think.
Oh, let me take this as well.
Uh, probably here?
Yeah.
Nice!
Sweet.
We're doing well.
Oh, yeah.
Gehenna!
I could just teleport to the boss room.
If I wanted to.
But I don't want to.
He...
He tonked me.
Yeah, okay, dude.
Okay, dude.
It was an inanimate object.
Of course it was.
West.
What?
Oh, no.
I want a pill.
What's a man?
Range down.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I really hate having the mark.
I wish I didn't have it.
I have made a mistake.
Taking it.
Technology.
Okay, I like that.
That's more like it.
This makes it way easier to aim as well now.
We don't have that much money.
We have some money.
Battery pack?
Huh, that is actually kind of sweet.
But...
Champion belt.
There's a lot of damage.
That is solid.
We need a couple coins more.
We can probably get it here.
The three dollar battery is also kind of enticing.
I'll be back.
Ooh, that looks like money to me.
Wait, there's spiky rocks.
I don't care.
Oh, no.
Wait, what is this?
Oh, I see.
Wait, I'm not...
Wait, what?
I'm confused.
So we go right now.
I think we're done, guys.
I think we're done.
I hate to say it.
We need to find a significant amount of battery now.
In fact, I may have to say goodbye to the champion belt and get the other one.
Just for the health.
I need to go back.
You know what, I need this bomb in here.
Oh, no.
This needs to be timed correctly.
Can't do it yet.
Nice.
Okay, enjoy these.
No money.
What about secrets?
How am I going to find the last coin?
I saw a couple blue flames earlier.
I do want to destroy those.
Oh, there's also a bomb there.
Wow.
Oi, yo, yo.
Oh, man.
Can I do this?
I may have to...
Wait, wait.
What do you think?
If I put it here...
Do this first.
Okay, and now...
What?
Why isn't it coming out?
Okay, I don't understand.
Whatever.
Huge.
Fuck.
Piss.
I spent it.
It's gone.
Just get over it.
What do you mean?
You have spent our savings.
At doorstop.
No, I want my current one.
Okay, we're getting some energy here.
We've got to play precise now.
We need to farm energy.
I'm not even sure what hit me there.
Wait, that was it?
Okay.
Not great.
There's another...
Yeah, there you are.
Oh,
chest.
I'm excited.
Yes.
It's one for Blackheart as well.
I want bombs.
I need more bombs.
Yes.
We also got to look for the key.
It's somewhere here.
Where's that heart?
There's a heart in here.
There it is.
Oh, I can't get it.
That's too bad.
The question is, where do I go out?
Here we go.
Okay, we're gaining HP.
Just what we need right now.
I got hit, man.
Yes,
that's huge.
HP, man.
I love it.
I need more of that right now.
Ooh, this one.
I can't do it.
I can't sacrifice my HP for that.
It's spiky.
Okay.
That's definitely worth.
Thank you.
Would be cool if you could blow open the chests, you know?
And not take damage from the spikes.
And become saved.
Let his light inside you cleanse your soul.
You are insane.
What's that?
Another, no wait, Empress?
I have Emperor.
I want this.
Wharf.
Fires the high damage explosive poison shot?
I've never had that before.
But I'm not going to use it.
Because I'm not sure what it...
Okay, maybe this is...
no.
Okay, yeah, that's...
I have to check what that was.
I want the Empress.
Oi!
Okay, we're getting HP.
But we're not really...
We're not finding a key yet, guys.
We kind of need a key.
I'm assuming it's just somewhere in this place, in this room.
You don't find it, you know?
It's like randomized.
Oh fuck.
I can't believe I got hit by that!
I have pretty good range.
Range is good.
Oh wait, this thing!
Yo!
Let's try it!
Oh wait, it doesn't do anything.
I guess there's just free damage.
Free damage for me.
Less speed, more damage...
No.
I think I need my speed.
We can't go lower.
This is a good amount of speed.
Too slow and it's going to be bad.
Okay, there's a couple of rooms I haven't found yet or explored.
You know, the technology is actually confusing me more than anything else.
Because it's messing with my brain on where actually I'm aiming.
Hey!
Let's do this!
Imagine if this thing drops a brimstone right now.
I would be so happy.
Lucky rock!
Oh well, that's kind of useless for me.
What is that?
Emergency contact?
No, this one is still better.
Please stop picking that up.
Jawbreaker!
No.
And that was that.
Load up.
There's a room left.
Possibly two.
I think this may have been the XL floor.
Look how big it is.
What?
No.
Dude, getting hit just now could have been the end of this run.
Sometimes it's up to like half a heart at the end, you know?
Everything matters.
Okay, good.
That gave me a lot of battery though.
I need more high HP enemies.
Like that.
Beautiful.
Keep charging.
Wow.
Ooh, another one of these.
I mean, I got a little bit of money left.
Rusted key.
Chance of finding keys is room clear rewards.
Maybe I need that.
I don't know.
It could increase my chances.
But it's just going to be the keys, keys, right?
I'm excited.
Wait, do I want that?
Hey, I love this one.
Should we get a black heart out of it?
That is a W right there.
Wait, how is this going to work?
Hold on.
Yeah, how about no?
That is horrible.
Absolutely not.
Can you imagine playing like that?
And now we go right.
I forgot where the light was.
No, I didn't.
It's in the left.
Oh, I just saw a tinted rock.
I saw it.
Look at it.
Sick.
Maybe there's more.
I got to keep an eye out for that.
Now, whatever.
Go!
I need you.
Yeah, let's blow a scout.
That is sorry, Isaac.
So it seems like if you charge up your battery, or you're active and you use it in the room, and then you do damage after that, it's not actually going to contribute to charging your item.
That sucks.
Like, why not?
I mean, now we're rich.
Shouldn't have blown that guy up now.
Damn.
I actually thought about it as well, you know?
Like, maybe I shouldn't blow this up in case I find a bunch of money.
I was like, nah, probably not.
Then right after, we find the money.
The good news is our HP is looking stellar.
And we're full HP now.
Please be the sun.
Actually, no, the sun is not good for me.
Ah, higher offense.
I think the Empress is actually better for me.
Because it's like sustained damage I get for a long period against the last boss.
It's more valuable.
I'm going to get HP from charging my active during the boss fight.
So there's that.
What are these guys... Why are they just standing still?
Like, aha, I don't care.
Ex-lax.
Don't get hit now.
Teleport to the secret room.
Why not?
Oh, okay.
Not exactly very exciting.
So that's where the light is.
We're going to go grab this Empress card and then leave.
Okay.
Here we go.
Home.
We made it.
Child's heart.
No, red hearts are bad for me.
Well, I mean, I can't use them.
Okay.
Well, shit, we don't have a key, man.
Fuck.
Well, what then?
What now?
What about?
Like, I'm not even sure what the fuck.
Why don't we have a key?
I checked literally every room.
Oh, I can't even take this.
That's funny.
I need a red heart for that.
Here we go.
We're going to park the mark on the TV.
I'm just going to chill.
We got the mantle now.
Empress time.
Get some HP.
Dude, I can just sit here because I destroyed projectiles.
I have that ability.
Wait, what?
You're done, son.
Come on, then.
I forget what you do.
Are you the...
Okay, you're that guy.
Got it.
Crap.
Okay, he mad now.
He mad now.
Holy shit.
This guy's going to do the glaives.
Yeah.
But I actually destroyed those, so I could maybe just sit back or something.
Nah, this is fine.
We're chilling.
Come on, man.
Bring it on.
I'm an expert at this guy.
Oh no, my cursor doesn't travel with the screen.
Guess it doesn't matter, honestly.
I love that I can seize HP.
I mean, I'm not going to die here.
There's no way I can die.
There is no way.
Keep healing.
Can I appear on the left, I guess?
Alright, it's not even close, guys.
This guy has nothing on me.
The cloak of revelations, baby.
Does it again.
It's too strong.
Yeah!
Unfortunately, we didn't find a key, so what the hell?
We did unlock something.
That's nice.
Yo, I wonder, actually...
If that is deterministic.
Because...
Wait a minute.
Who did I just play?
I wonder if there is a specific unlock associated with each of these marks that you get.
You know, let's say you have Eve, and you do...
I don't know.
Satan.
Or Isaac, you know?
Killing them, I mean.
Maybe there's like a specific unlock tied to that.
I don't know if it's actually random.
I'm going to do another one.
I think I want to do...
We don't have a lot of marks on Eulith.
Wait, how are we not killed Mom?
Or the heart, I mean.
Wait, what?
How does that even make sense?
Eden...
Judas doesn't have any.
Well, he has some, but not a lot.
Oh, I guess, and that mark is...
Killing the beast.
The little page there.
That makes sense, I guess.
I'm not sure what that box is in the center.
I don't have any on Jacob and Esau.
Let's do that one.
I've got none on this.
Oh, there's actually a bunch of...
Item, space...
Space and cute rice.
Hold.
Wait, what?
Oh, nice!
Ah, okay.
Okay, that's actually kind of big.
That's much better than last time I did this.
Okay, and then we have move.
Bomb is normal.
But we're both going to place a bomb, I guess.
An item.
Okay.
We have a question mark right now, which I think means we don't know what items we're going to pick up.
That's bad.
That's real bad.
This is a very unique character.
Wait, alright, that's how you do it.
Get away from me.
Okay, sleep, sleep, sleep.
Dude, I can't hit these guys.
Okay, there we go.
Man, this is scary.
And if I die on one of them, we die.
Like, completely.
The run is over.
I think red guy is the guy with the heart and the bottom right.
He's out.
Kind of want to go home with this guy.
Sinus infection.
Booger tears.
Cool.
Uh, I could go step.
I'm actually going to do it.
Two steps.
Maybe I'll come back and do some more.
Wow, who's moving fast?
Scary.
Oh my
god, stop getting stuck.
Okay, we got some money.
Whoo, nice.
Oh god!
That's scary.
Use diver chance to gain scatole.
I think I want to put that on...
Esau.
You stink.
We have ten coins.
Wow.
Really want to save for this one.
Actually, we can destroy this, I guess.
Oh!
Let's put it on...
Uh, this guy.
Nightlight, okay.
Not bad.
I do like the nightlight.
The pogers.
Oh crap.
I thought the nightlight would have an effect there, but it didn't.
Esau is having trouble, man.
He's almost dead.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh, you picked that up.
I'm going to actually let Esau take this one.
Yeah, HP up.
That's what I was hoping for.
Big chance of HP up when getting boss reward, right?
Okay, now, we go down.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
I can't not see those as tits.
Like someone is squeezing their tits and the little poop packages are coming out, you know?
That animation is so confusing.
We just lost all our demon chance!
No!
I wasn't focusing, I was thinking about tits.
Go!
You!
Actually, you're still here.
Hey, hey, not bad, huh?
I'm going to wait with that heart.
The potential is huge with this character, by the way.
Oops, let's not pick it up.
I suck!
What was I thinking?
A pushpin.
Uh, yeah.
Chance to fire toothshots.
Increases with luck, huh?
So that would be Jacob that needs this one.
By the way, I'm assuming the white guy is Jacob, I don't know.
Could be the other way around.
Destroy that.
I like.
Wait, uh, I don't want to use my key on that.
Oh shit, yeah, I mean, this is bad.
Nightlight, do your thing.
I wish the nightlight would just light in the direction I'm shooting and not in the direction I'm facing, you know?
We'll probably make it too strong.
Uh, yeah, you know what?
Let's go.
I feel it.
That pause is not affected by nightlight.
Nice.
More range?
Who has less range?
Oh, I can also check on the left.
Okay, yeah, good.
So, wait, what happened?
What did I just...
Oh, I held down control.
That's what happened.
Okay, let's go.
I thought three things just spawned out of nowhere.
Catacombs.
Let's do fight room.
Ouroboros, absolutely not.
I gotta Ouroboros me, huh?
Oh, no.
No, drop it, drop it!
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
You need to grab that.
And I grab these.
And then we move.
I could also just leave one of these guys in the corner and just control the other character.
That's probably not very ideal.
Unless he's about to die, I mean...
There's an argument that could be made.
She has to do this.
Flap behavior.
Chaos!
Oh!
That could be awesome!
I wanna put this on Esau.
He has the most damage.
Sick.
Wait, they're not affected by...
Oh, they are affected by my life.
Ahhh!
That was a very risky move there.
Shit.
Dude, Ezal's about to die.
I don't like this.
Wait, we can shoot rocks.
Let's not forget.
Dude, man, come on.
Wait, where'd he go?
Did he die?
Finally.
Uh, let's put this on Ezal.
Wait, how do I use this again?
Sick.
I was hoping for a health up, but, you know, I'll take it.
Oh, boss detected.
Let's do it.
Ah, but wait, with one heart?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go.
The husk.
I forget what he does.
Shit.
Dude, Ezal!
Focus.
Align, Align!
Thank God!
What?
How speed?
Speed is the same.
Okay.
We share that at least.
Oh my God.
Go find some HP.
Do we have any?
No, we don't.
Maybe in the shop.
Maybe here.
Fuck this game.
I picked the heart up on the rocket!
Ah!
Oh, I thought it was milk.
I need milk.
Maybe I'll buy this.
No.
Ezal, I'm leaving you behind.
Good luck.
I'm going alone.
I can't bring you with me.
I can't do it.
I need HP now.
Oh shit.
Oh my God.
No.
We're not doing that.
Are we done?
Oh man, that's scary.
Thank God there was no primstone.
No, no, Ezal!
You idiot!
Go again.
We go again.
I hate Ezal.
I do.
I don't like him.
He plays like shit.
It should be more like Jacob.
And I gave Ezal all the best items, and yet he failed me.
There's a piece of shit.
I cannot believe it.
There's nothing I want.
Maybe coupon, but too expensive.
Oh no, it's the shit item.
Oh man.
Ah, whatever.
That's extra bad on this character.
Oh!
Surprised me there.
Imagine if they had different speeds.
That would really suck.
That would make this character unplayable.
I'm glad that's not the case.
Okay.
I got one key.
Let's use it.
Okay.
Good amount of money.
There's a chance we get to 15.
Especially if we donate blood.
Oh, and get that.
No.
Oh, that's definitely for Ezal.
Nice.
But we still need a coin.
Coin, coin, coin, coin, coin.
Can we get it?
Curse room.
Maybe.
That's risky.
Or we look for secrets.
Maybe here.
I'll check the other sides.
Okay, that's good.
That's good.
What about here?
Wonderful!
Okay, this could work.
I gotta be careful.
Line them up like this.
Wonderful!
Come on, money, money, money!
Damn!
Mom's foot.
Sure.
Balls of steel.
Pheromones.
We don't have a bomb.
I can't... Oh man, that's so sad.
Okay.
I'm gonna step into the curse room.
This is my last ditch effort.
Oh, grab that.
Wish me luck.
What even is that?
Please die.
Uh, contract.
Uh, yeah, okay.
I'll go for that.
The thing is, uh, okay, here's the deal.
We're gonna maximize the shit out of this now.
We're gonna say fuck the coupon.
I'm gonna get another buffer on Jacob.
I'm also gonna buy that pill on ESO.
Nice.
Okay, grab that.
And we go.
Yeah, at least this way maybe we can get like an angel or something.
Actually, I think it's maybe better to go for demons.
Because if you think about it, we have twice the age people than normal, right?
So sacrifice to the angel.
I mean, to the demon.
Duke of Flies.
Okay, that's for Jacob.
What's that?
Okay.
Let me see.
That one is broken remote.
Tricks the teleport effect.
No.
The magician.
Uh, we can give that to ESO.
Appill.
Bam.
No demon.
That sucks.
Okay, seller two.
100% demon now.
And we both have buffers.
This is big.
It's beautiful.
It's bold.
This is how it goes wrong.
Bob's brain or mutant spider?
I think if I get mutant spider, the problem is it's going to be distinct when I shoot.
You know what I mean?
So it's going to be like my one character is going to shoot one stream of tears.
The other one's going to shoot this weird four tears at once.
So it's going to be weird to handle.
I think I have to choose.
But then again, familiar that charges in the direction I think is fine.
Oh, so this is dependent on the one I pick it up with.
I don't like that at all.
Dude, I kind of want to leave both.
Am I crazy?
I hate the... Okay, maybe that one could be okay.
It depends how it feels.
Where's the one?
No, go on this guy then.
Wait, what?
I can shoot.
I can have both.
Oh, well, in that case, give me that one.
Both ones, kids.
Why?
Why is that happening?
I don't like it, man.
I knew I shouldn't have taken it.
Fuck.
Okay, we can't take damage now.
No buffer on Esau.
It's not that bad, actually.
It's not that bad.
It's okay.
I can live to... I can learn to love it.
Get out of here.
Nice.
Okay, we have not taken damage.
This is it.
Oh, this one is not that hard.
Come on, we can do this.
The world is cruel.
I didn't mean to open that.
Christ.
Fucking stupid ass little white thingies that float around and move in unpredictable patterns.
And stop getting desynced!
Why am I shooting melons?
Oh, wait, that's the thing I...
Okay.
Totally look like a melon to me, like a watermelon.
Stop getting desynced, please.
Thank you.
Ah, man.
Ah.
You know what?
Fuck it.
It's all over anyway.
Ah, maybe not.
I like it.
More pills!
I like it!
I don't like that one.
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Hate when they get stuck.
Oh.
Library!
I'll be back for that.
Dude, I hate the quadruple shot.
I knew I shouldn't have taken it.
She's bad.
Oh, the range is terrible on it, too.
Okay, so wait, let me see.
Ooh, a cheap pill.
Now you've got my attention.
Ah!
Oh, okay.
Wouldn't it be funny if only one of us get teleported away?
I'm not done with that room.
I'm going to buy a heart, I think.
I'll also pick this up.
Wait, three books?
That's crazy.
Wait, why didn't I get the buff?
Oh, maybe it's probably just on one character, then.
So I have to sort of... Wait, how do I drop the other one?
Oh, like this, maybe?
Okay, fine, I'll calculate!
Two out of three.
Which one are you missing?
I'm so confused right now.
So wait, yellow, brown, X.
Yellow, brown, X.
Bad, baby, bad, baby!
Yellow, brown, wait, yellow, brown, X.
Let me think.
Wait, yellow?
Brown?
No, X.
No, brown?
X.
Why isn't it triggering?
I don't understand what the fuck is happening, bro.
This makes no sense at all.
Uh, I don't even know what I want.
Maybe the monster manual is not too bad, actually.
Less micromanagement.
Yeah, let me have that.
The Bible is good.
I like the Bible.
Man, that was...
That made no sense at all to me.
Apparently it doesn't work when you have two characters.
I don't know why.
I wonder though, if I activate flying, it's probably just gonna be on one character.
But who knows?
We're going home!
Cat.coms.
We could have lost all demon right then and there.
Also, I should be using, uh, that one now.
Yeah.
Did we?
Okay, we did not get hit on Esau.
Thank the Lord above.
Ah, it's over.
Yeah.
You come into a room like that, it's over.
How do you even avoid anything?
Like, fuck you, game.
Impossible.
I hate that, man.
Getting put in impossible situations.
Oh, shit, I released them!
Yes, pills.
I want that.
How about I also want that?
Whatever.
Open your mouth.
Ranch poison to you.
Interesting.
I'll have that.
I have no idea how it's going.
Like, I don't, I have no idea.
Oh, it's open.
What even was that?
The fuck just happened?
Once the manual.
I can't unsee the watermelon.
Like, if you squint your eyes, squint your eyes right now and just look at it's moving around, you know?
It's a watermelon.
Do I go in?
I don't!
Wait, I'm almost dead.
Well, shit.
This is the end of me.
Wow.
I need some HP here, bro.
Not, not the bombs.
Okay.
HP, HP.
Nice.
Definitely buying that.
Don't even want to, look at the other items.
Okay.
Speed up.
I do enjoy those.
I can't afford it.
Maybe I can.
I cannot.
Oh!
At least it was the Esau that got hit.
I'm happy about that.
This is nerve-wracking playing this character.
Okay, here we go.
Pick up, pick up.
Nice.
Solid.
Just before the... Oh, shit.
Double trouble.
Is that because we are also double trouble?
It's a double, double whammy.
I'm using the Bible.
You can't stop me.
We are desynx.
I hate the quad shot so much, dude.
There's no range on this.
Wait, there's little guys?
Oh, it's my little guy.
More tears, less shots, beat plus health.
I think it's for Jacob.
Jakob.
Oh, but look at this.
That's for Esau.
Wow, everyone gets something.
You get something, you get something.
Delicious.
Curse of the blind means we don't see what the items are.
Okay, that's nice to have that for later.
In close range, the quadruple shot is actually pretty nice.
It's good at pushing people away, you know?
Oh, god, we got detected!
Scary when that happens.
We still have 100% demon.
We got to be real careful.
We haven't even gotten a single deal in this run.
Is this the run?
We got a buffer?
Just on one of us, though.
If I can get a second buffer, we could be cooking here.
Focus, focus.
Start a step, start a step.
Beautiful.
Pill.
Wow!
Okay, man, we are so fucking lucky right now with the pills.
This is great.
That was so lucky.
Holy shit, dude.
Wow.
Where's the boss at?
I need the boss right now.
I can't handle this anxiety anymore.
Damn, son.
Random buddy.
Okay.
I'll take it.
Uh-oh.
I saw my life flash before my eyes.
Where's the boss at?
Okay, as long as we're here, we're safe.
There we go.
Come on.
Focus.
Mega fatty?
He's not too bad.
We can do it.
We got to stay on the move, though, because he jumps, and it's very scary when he jumps.
Please puke.
I beg you.
There's the jump.
Yes!
Demon!
I will take it on this guy.
Oh, no, I can't see what it is.
Oh, crap.
Okay, we're gonna give one to each.
Guys, a baton to you.
And for the other guy, ceremonial ropes.
Everyone gets loot in the dungeon.
Oh, wait.
Do we only have black hearts?
Oh, shit.
Yikes.
That's bad.
That's a bad one.
Guys, it's not good.
This is problematic.
I'm just gonna go.
Just go, man.
Go.
At least we have more damage now.
That indirectly means more survival.
I'm so scared.
Holy crap.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Wow.
Oh, okay.
You're bombing.
What's happening?
Oh, can we make these things stop moving?
Oh, no.
I changed it.
Whatever.
Just leave.
Golden shits.
I got hit on the wrong character there.
What do we have?
Perth Row.
Re-rolls all item pedestals.
Okay, so if we find demon, we can re-roll.
Potentially.
Wait, who do I need?
What is that card right there?
High priestess.
I don't care about that.
Oh, that's gotta be on Jacob.
Sick.
Get out of here.
Oh, that was scary.
Do we have a little chubby?
Oh, more pills.
We don't know what it is.
Another one.
Just use it.
Why did I get hit on that character?
You know what?
I'm gonna go in here with Isao.
Interesting.
I am not going to do that.
Nope.
No, thanks.
Man!
These goddamn objects.
Give me a million enemies instead of one static object.
My brain can't handle it, man!
Make me a father.
Drop it!
Laser!
Laser man.
The kids have lasers in their shoes.
No!
We lost all demon!
I'm in pain!
Who's this little guy?
I don't know what's happening.
Leo!
I like it!
Oh, that's also interesting.
I will eat all the skulls.
Open your mouth.
Oh yeah!
Okay, this is for Isao.
Hold on.
Jackie, you can't jump up now.
Food is soon.
I'm busy.
Open.
There we go.
Not that we need the buffer anymore.
That train has driven.
No, left the station.
You know what I mean.
Oh, wait!
We got a special box!
Consume to spawn two random angel room pedestal items.
Oh my god!
If a devil deal has been taken, spawns one angel room item and...
Okay.
The star is depleted.
It can only be charged by picking up... Okay, I like it!
Let's drop the monster manual.
I say no to that.
Yep.
Healing we don't need.
Go.
Shit balls.
Here we go.
Blood.
Wow!
I've never seen that before.
That's a new one.
And my life.
Bro, I'm trying to dodge blue projectiles as well, but I guess they're mine.
I don't know what it was happening here.
Now it's time for mom.
We have magician, ace of clubs.
Just do it.
I can't handle looking at it.
Yep.
Oh yeah, I can eat rocks.
The sun!
Not bad.
This character is very difficult to play.
Wait, I wonder if I could have eaten that box.
Shit!
I was trying to pick it up with the other guy.
What just exploded?
What the fuck is exploding?
That wasn't a bomb from him.
Explosivo.
I want to put this on the guy with the most tears, which means Iso actually.
Oh wow.
Okay, I think we just...
No, wait, we need teleport.
Teleports.
But chance of getting that.
It's not too high.
I don't even know if I want anything in there.
I mean, of course, the blue heart is good, but
unidentified, huh?
Okay, not bad.
Stay behind me.
A die shard.
Now that's kind of intriguing.
I'll take it.
Look at that one.
There's an X on it.
Look, there's going to be an item in here.
Huh?
The fool!
That's what I needed, baby.
Uh, wait, what does the dice shard do again?
B-rolls all items and pickups.
I think, I guess I exchanged this.
No, you know what, I'm going to use the sun now to reveal the map and then I'm going to pick it up with...
...with all
the rocks.
Oh, pills.
That doesn't work on, unfortunately, it doesn't work on the alabaster box.
Teleports to a random room.
Wow.
Ah, crap.
Let's not forget this one either.
No, I think I'm just going to go.
I'm good.
Oh, I can fly in here, by the way.
School back.
Sick.
Eight ball.
Oh, nice.
Huge.
Ancient recall as well.
Ancient recall.
Watch this.
You have fortune and
death.
Oh, now I have USB issues again.
I don't know what's happening.
Hold on.
Is there like a loose cable?
I plucked it out.
Hopefully, I didn't break anything.
Okay, I'm going to eat all these.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
That's huge.
Oh, no.
Dude, these stupid rocks in the center is like the hardest enemy in the game.
Change my mind.
Change my fucking mind on that.
Bouncing tier.
I'll take it.
Made it.
Well, we can go to the boss now, actually.
I feel good.
Let's do it.
I believe.
Pheromones, I don't need that.
Mom!
Are you going to stomp?
Are you going to stomp your feet?
Clap your hands?
Form a brand new dance?
Oh, I almost got stomped there.
No demon, unfortunately.
Damn.
That's sad.
I guess I'll take this one.
And then we teleport.
There we go.
Now we're just going to get lucky finding a key.
That's going to be the biggest thing.
If we can get lucky with that, then we're rolling, you know?
All right.
You're going to laser.
Oh, interesting.
Wait, what?
Oh.
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh, I did not understand this room.
Now I do.
You got to destroy these for a chance and
multiplying.
Give me some blue hearts.
I need them bad.
Like real bad.
Come on.
What is hitting me?
There we go.
Pick it up with these out.
Okay.
We're charging the box.
Slowly, but surely it's happening.
What do you think?
How I only have two hearts on Jacob?
Wait, what's happening?
I can't shoot.
Oh.
That was hairy.
I think we're done here.
Don't find some healing right now.
It is pretty much over.
Wait, wait, two items.
Bloodsucker.
Now I couldn't pick up two items.
Weird.
Uh, I don't know how to do this.
Wait.
Go!
Wow, that's scary.
Oh man, I missed the room.
Oh, it's mine.
Okay, fuck it.
Give me healing.
More healing.
We're distinct.
Oh.
At least we have full health again.
The leech is doing its job here.
Okay, he needs bombs.
I can provide that.
Don't walk into that accidentally.
Oh god, I didn't mean to go in here.
Oh no.
Bad gas.
No, I need health up.
Dude, I'm in deep shit.
There's a shop up here.
Oh no.
It's not an actual shop.
I think I'm cooked.
How am I gonna do this without fucking it up?
Maybe I... I desync like this.
I'm too scared.
We're gonna desync like this instead and walk in with you.
Okay, we need that.
Charge the box.
Uh,
wait, I would rather take that on this character.
I'm not feeling good.
An item?
Oh, it's the page that leads me to the... yeah, okay.
That's notes.
It just occurred to me actually that the voiceover right now...
Maybe the note, actually.
That's what's written on the note, I guess?
No, no, they have a conversation, so it's not.
It's back and forth.
All right, now we gotta find some hearts, man.
I need to activate that alabaster box.
I really do need... okay, this is huge.
Yeah, heal up like that.
I need the leech to do its job.
Leech, go!
Whatever.
Actually, the leech only works for Jacob, not Esau.
It's hard.
Judgment spawns a beggar.
Yes, yes, actually!
That's massive.
Gotta spend my money, right?
Ooh, that's huge!
Take that on Jacob.
Very nice.
We can go up here.
Not bad.
Yeah, okay, that was it.
Can we find my blue hearts, man?
That's what I need.
Okay, that's also good.
Oh, wait, I'm spawning bombs from the enemies.
I'm gonna eat these.
Black hearts, come on, black heart me.
Dang.
Ooh, this one's gonna be tough.
Oh, you're right, I can rock through rocks, so that actually was not that hard.
Wait, what did I just pick up?
I just picked up some keys, I think.
Lost cork?
We're not leaving any creep puddles, let's just leave it.
Huge!
Charge it!
Damn.
This way.
We're almost fully charged.
Oh my god, we're almost dead!
That's so huge, we got that heart.
Stay in a float here.
Eat these.
Uh, wait, yeah, go this way.
Leave, good, leave!
We'll be fine without you.
Abandon us like the bandit yourself.
Tagas!
Uh, that's for him.
We're almost fully charged.
More money.
Let's all pick up this again.
Oh, no.
Damn.
Oh, that sucks.
Keys!
Oh, I got 11 keys.
We can do this.
Chest.
Aw.
Paperclip.
Uh, I mean, we don't have anything on ESO anyway.
Yes, we'll take it.
We're gonna use all our keys here.
Okay.
63 coins.
What's that?
Cancer.
Ooh, uh...
Wait, who do I want to give that to?
I guess...
Jacob.
And we can give this to him instead.
I like that.
And that's it.
Let's get out.
I need a couple more blue hearts here.
Can we get it?
That's the question.
Caves too.
We still have a little bit of a way to go here.
That's good.
Hookworm, no thanks.
Not a fan of that one.
No, Jackie.
Very soon.
I'll be there in just a sec.
I gotta finish this run, and then we go play and eat, okay?
Jackie is at my legs.
Just, you know, pushing herself up against my leg.
Aha!
Here we go, baby!
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Let me see.
I need to do this in a good way.
Ready?
Wait, how am I actually gonna get that?
Wait, how the... how the hell am I gonna get that one?
Jackie!
There we go.
Maybe if I...
Bro, I have... we gotta keep trying with the bombs.
Okay, now it's straight.
Now we just need to...
Watch this.
Yeah!
It's charged!
There we go.
Here we go.
You ready?
Uh...
What is that item?
I can't see it.
Spear of Destiny grants a spear melee weapon that deals contact damage to enemies.
The spear sometimes inflicts fear on enemies it touches.
Okay.
I guess I'll take it.
Oh!
Oh, that's a big spear!
I mean, it's not like I have any...
Oh, that's also very nice.
I have no desire to walk into melee range, to be honest with you.
Not bad, eh?
Oh, here we go, baby!
Tell me for the other one as well.
Oh my god, that's huge.
Both get something.
I'm healing there, that's good.
And now we get out.
If we can find the light.
I think it was over here somewhere.
But here's the thing, we still need to find a damn key.
Like, I'm so unlucky with that right now.
Also, where is the light?
Here.
Let's go.
You need to repent.
You need to confess your sins and become saved.
Let his light inside you cleanse your soul.
Boom!
You are taking this too far.
You are ready for your salvation.
Come, pray with us, Isaac.
Don't do it, don't pray with him.
Losing a lot of buffers here for no reason.
Did I just get hit?
No way.
Ah, we were decent!
Oh my god, I'm playing some...
Fucking hell, we got decent there, hard.
No more buffers.
Not that we need buffers, but it's just nice to have for the boss, right?
There's one more room I didn't explore.
I mean, we gotta explore everything.
Because I gotta get that damn key.
And they spawn in these rooms.
Oh, what's that?
Uh, I don't think we're gonna see any more rooms anyway, so...
Boo.
Okay, let's go.
I could grab this money.
Maybe I'll find a use for it at some point.
Oh, that's not...
That's a bomb.
Careful.
We're decent!
That's so scary.
Especially against this type of enemy.
Tactical bomb usage.
Nah, okay, move on.
Oh, I got keys for you, buddy.
Oh, crap.
No, it blew him up!
That's so sad.
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho!
This game is nerve-wracking!
Wow, he has a lot of HP!
What?
That guy was crazy.
Let's go...
There's a little room he missed here.
What is that one?
Bombs have a 10% chance to spawn a bomb on detonation.
Uh, no.
I don't want that.
It could maybe be good against the beast.
But what I have right now is better, I think.
Oh god, this is bad.
I can't fucking...
I'm overwhelmed by all this shit on my screen right now.
Like, what is happening?!
Where are the shots coming from, man?!
Okay, there you are.
Insane.
Like, I break down mentally.
In those rooms.
I can't handle it.
There's too much fucking crap on my screen, dude.
I can't see anything.
It's honestly pissing me off.
And it all ends like that, dude.
Fuck.
That's so sad.
No, it's not- It has nothing to do with Jakob and Iso.
That's just a universal thing.
Like, when there's a room like that, and the enemies are off-screen, and they're shooting random-ass projectiles in random-ass directions, it's just not fun.
You know?
I don't know where the fuck they're coming from.
I can't get close, because there's projectiles everywhere.
It's just annoying.
Do
you often feel lost and forgotten?
Uh...
Maybe?
Sometimes?
Right now, I felt lost and forgotten, for sure.
But normally, no.
Thanks for your question.
Yeah, off-screen enemies are super annoying, man.
You don't know what they're doing, you know?
I feel like they shouldn't have a range that's bigger than what you can see on the screen.
But I'm obviously just, you know, venting now, because I lost the run in a very...
in a very horrific way.
But yeah.
Most of your complaints of mods to fix that?
Yeah, but I don't want to install mods to make the game easier.
I feel like that's kind of weak, you know?
I don't know about that.
I don't like that.
I'd rather just play it as it's intended, even though the intended way is annoying.
Like, I am frustrated, but it's okay.
It's part of the game to be frustrated.
Okay.
It's a normal thing.
It doesn't mean anything more than the fact that I...
I'm just playing a video game, and I died in an annoying way, so I'm venting, you know?
That's all that is.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, everyone experiences, you know, frustration in games like this, I guess.
Is Sims or Isaac harder?
Mentally, Sims is way harder.
Because in this game, in this moment right now, I was completely overwhelmed by the stuff on my screen for approximately 17 seconds.
In Sims, imagine a screen filled with projectiles coming from all directions, but for a sustained four hours.
That's what Sims is.
You don't have to physically dodge it with your keyboard, but you're mentally dodging it.
And it's very tough, okay?
Trust me, people that are shit-talking Sims have never played it.
That game is ruthless.
And I want to see you get to attend friends, okay?
Let's see you make 10 family friends while getting promoted and keeping your shit up.
I'm done, ranting.
They're both difficult in their own way, yeah.
Is there a specific game you seek to play next?
Like with Sims, you said I need a more chill game alongside Isaac?
Yeah, see how that turned out.
I mean, the game can't be chill, but mostly it's actually kind of stressful.
I don't know if there's anything specific I seek next.
I haven't really thought too much about it.
I'm just taking things as they come.
Sims 2 is definitely easier, though, right?
But didn't forget Claire.
Who's Claire?
Talos is a game I could see myself playing very soon, actually.
But there's another game that I really am itching to play right now.
I'm not gonna tell you what it is.
What do you mean, who's Claire?
Minecraft?
Well, that's on July 17th.
That's when Minecraft starts.
Right.
Don't believe that.
Mujanix is not chill.
Okay, then it's not gonna be Mujanix.
What about Elden Ring deals?
See, I already played that.
I've heard Hotline Miami has really good music, but I haven't played it.
In fact, I think I've heard some of the music from Hotline Miami at some point.
I don't know in which connection, but I have heard it before.
But I've never played the game.
No, I don't want to- no, Minesweeper makes me- honestly, it makes me want to puke.
Like, just thinking about it makes me go, oh, that's so boring.
Like, I'm bored just thinking about it.
I don't want to play Minesweeper.
Red Dead Redemption 2 streams?
No, I'm playing that offline.
I feel like in a story game like that, it's just much better for local recording.
I mean, guys, I haven't really decided what to play next.
I'm still thinking about it.
I'm still having fun in Isaac.
But as you can tell, I'm slowing down a little bit with it.
Because, you know, there's getting fewer and fewer things to unlock as time goes on.
And I'm also really having trouble with my allergies lately.
Like, there have been days where I've been wanting to stream, and I just couldn't.
Because I knew it would be a shit show.
Like, my nose is running, my eyes are itchy, my throat is, you know, has slime in it or whatever, and I can't speak properly.
It's absolute hell.
Today is one of the better days.
And I'm, like, pumped up with anti-histamines right now, and nose drops and fucking eye drops and shit, or nasal sprays.
It's bad right now.
Uh, I don't know about semi-blind with Isaac.
Do you mean, like, when I ask you guys for, like, what to do next and stuff?
If that's what you're talking about, maybe?
We'll see.
But it could also be a cool forever game, you know, to have.
Even today, I had to sneeze, like, at least 10 times, but you never noticed, because I'm a fucking sneaky ninja.
I'm so good at muting myself and quickly sneezing, and then unmuting and continuing as if nothing happened.
You guys didn't know.
You guys had no idea that I sneezed 10 times today.
But I do want to play something very different next on the streams, you know, something very different from anything else.
I'm trying to think what that is.
I don't know what I want.
I know I want something.
It's like, you know you want junk food, but you don't know what kind of junk you want.
Minecra- That's not, that's not, uh, it needs to be, like, very different.
Yo, actually, a scary game on stream could be cool.
That's a good idea.
I don't think I've ever done that.
But maybe a shorter one.
Outlast, perhaps.
Yeah, I've heard good things about it.
Oh, Five Nights at Freddy's.
That could be one, yeah.
Is that a short game, guys?
How long is Five Nights at Freddy's?
But how is- Okay, I'm gonna be honest with you guys.
Guys, how is it only a few hours when I know that there are YouTube channels out there dedicated to this game?
How is it possible?
Like, it doesn't even make sense.
Oh, there's many different games of it, or...
Multiple games and challenges.
Okay, okay, I see.
I guess it's like a cult classic or something at this point.
Okay, well, that sounds pretty good.
Maybe I'll play that.
We'll see.
Maybe something else.
Maybe I'll come up with something completely out of left field.
Maybe something that rhymes with, uh...
I'm not even gonna say it, because it's too easy to figure out.
But, you know, something very different.
Maybe coming soon to streams.
And also something very familiar.
Both at the same time.
Guys, I'm gonna go feed my cat, because, uh...
It is like half an hour ago since she was supposed to be fed.
And it's also like half an hour ago since I was supposed to be fed.
So I'm gonna go do that.
Thank you for watching.
We're gonna have more streams in the future.
Especially when I feel better with my allergies, there's gonna be more streams.
But yeah, thank you for watching.
I'll see you next time.
Bye-bye.